

# How to reach me:

#### **Phone Number**

09564857491

#### **Email Address:**

bagaanferlez@gmail.com

#### Linkedin:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/ferlez2/

#### Address:

Kamagayan, Cebu City, Cebu

#### **Personal Profile**

I am a Virtual Assistant and Graphic Designer with robust problem-solving skills and proven experience in customer relation management and social media management with great practice of work ethics and professionalism. Willing to be trained in all new things.

## **Career Summary**

#### Office Clerk

Sisters of Mary School - Boystown August 2018 - March 2019

- Organized files and reports of the school related documents
- Created presentations and reports
- Assisted the school principal in all the various task

# **Executive Graphic Designer**

BroSis Cosmetics January 2019 - present

- Designed marketing materials and promotions
- Conceptualized designs for packaging
- Creates designs to promote on social media platforms

# **Virtual Assistant**

January 2019 - March 2021

- Managing social media platforms for promotions
- Creating landing pages and sales for the campaign
- Customer Relation Management
- Web Designing and Graphic Designing

## **Professional Skills and Tools**

## **Graphic Design:**

Adobe Photoshop, Illustrator, Canva

### **Email Marketing**

Klaviyo, Omnisend, Clubworx, Zipline

## **Social Media Management:**

Facebook ads, Creator Studio, Hootsuite,

### Web Design

WordPress, Joomla, Wix, Plugin

## **Apps Integrations/Automation**

**Xapier** 

#### **Customer Relation Management**

Facebook, Instagram, Clubworx, Zipline

## **Data Entry/ Organization**

Spreadsheet, Excel, Microsoft word,

#### **Communication Tools**

Skype, Zoom, Slack, Messenger

### **Task Management**

Trello, Monday

# **Educational Training**

# Sisters of Mary School - Boystown, Inc.

Major in Visual Graphic Design NCIII

- Enrolled since April 2014 to September 2019
- Taking up specialization courses in visual graphic design and multimedia

## **Character References**

# SIster Eva R. Aringo, SM.

School Principal, Sisters of Mary School - Boystown, Inc. Cell: 09474879326

# Mrs. Analyn Cavan

Assistant School Principal, Sisters of Mary School - Boystown, Inc. Cell: 09458219506